[2.5s] Start
[2.5s] 시작
[5s]
[7.5s] Twinkle, Twinkle, Little star
[7.5s] 반짝, 반짝, 작은 별
[10s]
[12.5s] Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
[12.5s] 반짝, 반짝, 작은 별,
[15s] How I wonder what you are.
[15s] 너는 정말로 놀라운 존재로구나.
[17.5s] Up above the world so high,
[17.5s] 저 높은 하늘 너머 세상 위에서,
[20s] Like a diamond in the sky.
[20s] 너는 다이아몬드처럼 빛나는 구나.
[22.5s]
[25s] Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
[25s] 반짝, 반짝, 작은 별,
[27.5s] How I wonder what you are.
[27.5s] 너는 정말로 놀라운 존재로구나.
[30s] When the blazing sun is gone,
[30s] 뜨거운 햇님이 잠들었을 때,
[32.5s] When he nothing shines upon,
[32.5s] 아무것도 빛을 비추지 않을 때,
[35s] Then you show your little light.
[35s] 너는 작은 빛을 보여주지.
[37.5s] Twinkle, twinkle, all the night.
[37.5s] 밤새도록 반짝, 반짝.
[40s]
[42.5s] Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
[42.5s] 반짝, 반짝, 작은 별,
[45s] How I wonder what you are.
[45s] 너는 정말로 놀라운 존재로구나.
[47.5s]
[50s] Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
[50s] 반짝, 반짝, 작은 별,
[52.5s] How I wonder what you are.
[52.5s] 너는 정말로 놀라운 존재로구나.
[55s] Up above the world so high,
[55s] 저 높은 하늘 너머 세상 위에서,
[57.5s] Like a diamond in the sky.
[57.5s] 너는 다이아몬드처럼 빛나는 구나.
[60s]
[62.5s] Twinkle, twinkle, little star,
[62.5s] 반짝, 반짝, 작은 별,
[65s] How I wonder what you are.
[65s] 너는 정말로 놀라운 존재로구나.
[67.5s]
[70s] End
[70s] 끝